<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-15" standalone="no"?><uc-export clientvers="11.0.0">
<DOCU name="PCK.AUTOMIC_ORACLE_OSB.PUB.DOC">
<HEADER state="1">
<Title>Package Documentation</Title>
<ArchiveKey1/>
<ArchiveKey2/>
<OH_SubType/>
</HEADER>
<DOCU_Docu state="1" type="text">
<DOC><![CDATA[About Automic's Oracle OSB Package
================================

Oracle Service Bus manages different types of services, and provides traditional message brokering across heterogeneous IT environments. With this package we automate the management of session and resources through various actions. These actions could further be used in a complex workflow to achieve the given business goal.

* Create/Activate/Destroy Session
* Import OSB Resource
* Execute Customization
* Delete Project

=Supported OSB versions=
Oracle Service Bus 11g and 12c

=Limitations=
No known limitations.

=Setup=

* The Agent should be setup on the target OSB instance.

* Oracle JDK 1.7 or higher must be installed on Agent OS and "java" must be set as executable on the same.

* Modify the Connection timeout parameter as per your environment. By default "CONNECTION_TIMEOUT" is defined as 60000. Value is defined in milliseconds. 0 means no timeout.

* You should have connection details to connect to Oracle OSB Services.


=Variables=
PCK.AUTOMIC_ORACLE_OSB.PRV.VARA.PACKAGE_PARAMETERS
* Connection timeout parameter can be configured in this variable. Value is defined in milliseconds. 0 means no timeout.

=Actions=
Following actions are supported for Oracle OSB

* Action Name: PCK.AUTOMIC_ORACLE_OSB.PUB.ACTION.CREATE_SESSION
* Action Description: This action is used to create a session in Oracle Service Bus.

* Action Name: PCK.AUTOMIC_ORACLE_OSB.PUB.ACTION.ACTIVATE_SESSION
* Action Description: This action is used to activate a session in Oracle Service Bus.

* Action Name: PCK.AUTOMIC_ORACLE_OSB.PUB.ACTION.DISCARD_SESSION
* Action Description: This action is used to destroy a session in Oracle Service Bus.

* Action Name: PCK.AUTOMIC_ORACLE_OSB.PUB.ACTION.IMPORT_RESOURCE
* Action Description: This action is used to import a resource into Oracle Service Bus.

* Action Name: PCK.AUTOMIC_ORACLE_OSB.PUB.ACTION.EXECUTE_CUSTOMIZATION
* Action Description: This action is used to execute customization into Oracle Service Bus.

* Action Name: PCK.AUTOMIC_ORACLE_OSB.PUB.ACTION.DELETE_PROJECT
* Action Description: This action is used to delete a Project in Oracle Service Bus]]></DOC>
</DOCU_Docu>
</DOCU>
</uc-export>